<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Indian Cricketers</string>

    <string-array name="name_of_player">
        <item>Virat Kohli</item>
        <item>Rohit Sharma</item>
        <item>MS Dhoni</item>
        <item>K.L. Rahul</item>
        <item>Rishabh Pant</item>
        <item>Jaspirit Bumrah</item>
        <item>Hardik Pandya</item>
        <item>Ravindra Jadeja</item>
        <item>Mohammad Shami</item>
        <item>Yuzvendra Chahal</item>
        <item>Bhuvneshwar Kumar</item>
        <item>Ishant Sharma</item>
        <item>Dinesh Kartik</item>
        <item>Kedar Jadhav</item>
        <item>Kuldeep Yadav</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="desc_mashrafe">Mortaza is the best fast-medium bowler and Parliment member of Bangladesh.
        He is a player who has come from the root label of the countryside by selecting of Grameen Phone.
        He emerged as a most successfull pace bowler in Bangladesh.
    </string>
    <string name="mashrafe_career">
        Mortaza made his debut in ODI cricket on 23 November 2001 and Test cricket on 8 November 2001
        against Zimbabwe.He was captain in one Test and seven One-Day Internationals(ODIs) between 2009 and
        2010,later he was bound to leave captaincy for injury.In his absence ,Shakib Al Hasan became captain
        of Bangladesh team.Undoubtedly ,he is the best pace bowler in pace bowler in the country and
        for his magnificent performance,he is called "Narail Express".He is regarded as the most popular
        player in the country.He showed his briliant performance as a captain of the Dhaka Gladiators in the
        BPL(Bangladesh Premier League).He is the winning captain of BPL for the first and second competition.

    </string>
    <string name="mash_retirement">
        Mashrafe announced his retirement from twenty20 internationals during the first twenty20
        game against Sri Lanka on 4 April 2017 among two matches second match will be last in an
        international t20 career.

    </string>

    <string name="desc_shakib_al_hasan">
        Bangladesh is now an established name in the Cricket World.There is a lot of players
    </string>

    <string name="virat_early_life">
        Virat Kohli was born on 5 November 1988 in Delhi into a Punjabi family. His father,
        Prem Kohli, worked as a criminal lawyer and his mother, Saroj Kohli, is a housewife.
        He has an older brother, Vikas, and an older sister, Bhavna.According to his family,
        when he was three-years old, Kohli would pick up a cricket bat, start swinging it and ask
        his father to bowl at him.
        Kohli was raised in Uttam Nagar and started his schooling at Vishal Bharti Public School.
    </string>

    <string name="virat_domestic_career">
        Kohli first played for Delhi Under-15 team in October 2002 in the 2002–03 Polly Umrigar
        Trophy. He was the leading run-scorer for his team in that tournament with 172 runs at an
        average of 34.40. He became the captain of the team for the 2003–04 Polly Umrigar Trophy and scored 390 runs in 5 innings at an average of 78 including two centuries and two
        fifties.In late 2004, he was selected in the Delhi Under-17 team for the 2003–04 Vijay
        Merchant Trophy. He scored 470 runs in four matches at an average of 117.50 with two hundreds
        and top-score of 251*.Delhi Under-17s won the 2004–05 Vijay Merchant Trophy in which Kohli
        finished as the highest run-scorer with 757 runs from 7 matches at an average of 84.11 with two
        centuries. In February 2006, he made his List A debut for Delhi against Services but did
        not get to bat.
    </string>

    <string name="virat_captency">
      Having found a place in India\'s Test squad for the tour of Australia in December 2011,
      Kohli top-scored with 132 in a tour match against Cricket Australia Chairman\'s XI to
      strengthen his case for a spot in the playing eleven ahead of Rohit Sharma. Batting
      at number 6, Kohli failed to go past 25 in the first two Tests, as his defensive technique
      was exposed.While fielding on the boundary during the second day of the second match,
      he gestured to the crowd with his middle finger for which he was fined 50% of his match fee by
      the match referee. He top-scored in each of India\'s innings in the third Test at Perth, with
      44 and 75, even as India surrendered to their second consecutive innings defeat.
  </string>

    <string name="virat_records">
        Kohli stood-in as the captain for the first ODI of the triangular series in the West Indies
        after Dhoni injured himself during the match. India lost the match by one wicket, and Dhoni
        was subsequently ruled out of the series with Kohli being named the captain for the remaining
        matches.In his second match as captain, Kohli scored his first hundred as captain, making 102
        off 83 balls against the West Indies at Port of Spain in a bonus point win for India.
        Many senior players including Dhoni were rested for the five-match ODI tour of Zimbabwe in
        July 2013, with Kohli being appointed captain for an entire series for the first time.In the
        first game of the series at Harare, he struck 115 runs from 108 balls, helping India chase down
        the target of 229 and winning the man of the match award.He batted on two more occasions in
        the series in which he had scores of 14 and 58 not out. India completed a 5–0 sweep of the
        series; their first in an away ODI series

    </string>
    <string name="rohit_early_life">
        Sharma was born on 30 April 1987 in Bansod, Nagpur, Maharashtra.His mother Purnima Sharma
        is from Visakhapatnam.His father Gurunath Sharma worked as a caretaker of a transport firm
        storehouse. Sharma was raised by his grandparents and uncles in Borivali because of his
        father\'s low income. He would visit his parents, who lived in a single-room house in
        Dombivli, only during weekends.He has a younger brother, Vishal Sharma.
    </string>
    <string name="rohit_personal_life">
        Sharma married Ritika Sajdeh in December 2015.They have a daughter.
    </string>
    <string name="rohit_domestic_career">
        Sharma made his List A debut for West Zone against Central Zone in the Deodhar Trophy at
        Gwalior in March 2005. Batting at number eight, he scored 31 (not out) as West Zone won by
        3 wickets with 24 balls remaining. Cheteshwar Pujara and Ravindra Jadeja made their debuts
        in the same match.It was Sharma\'s unbeaten innings of 142 in 123 balls against North
        Zone at Udaipur in the same tournament that brought him into the limelight.He visited
        Abu Dhabi and Australia with the India A squad and was then included among India\'s 30-member
        probables list for the upcoming ICC Champions Trophy tournament. although he did not make the
        final squad.
    </string>
    <string name="rohit_international_career">
        In November 2013, during Sachin Tendulkar\'s farewell series, Sharma made his test debut at
        Eden Gardens in Kolkata against the West Indies and scored 177, the second-best score on
        debut by an Indian behind Shikhar Dhawan (187).He followed it up with 111 (not out)
        in the second test at his home ground, the Wankhede Stadium in Mumbai.
    </string>
    <string name="rohit_t20_career">
        Sharma was included in the Indian squad for the 2007 ICC World Twenty20 and made his mark by
        scoring an unbeaten 50 from 40 deliveries against hosts South Africa in the quarter-finals.
        This enabled India to win the match by 37 runs and they went on to defeat Pakistan in the
        final, when Sharma scored 30 (not out) from 16 deliveries.
    </string>
    <string name="rohit_indian_premier_league">
        Sharma has been one of the most successful players in the Indian Premier League (IPL) as captain
        since 2013 of the Mumbai Indians, who have won the tournament four times under his leadership.
        He is currently (July 2019) one of ten players who have scored 4,000 career runs in the
        competition. Sharma has 4,898 with one century and is the third highest run scorer after Virat
        Kohli and Suresh Raina.
    </string>
    <string name="rohit_records">
        Sharma holds the world record for the highest individual score by a batsman playing in a
        one-day international match, having scored 264 against Sri Lanka at Eden Gardens, Kolkata,
        on 13 November 2014.He is the only player to have scored three double-centuries in this
        form of international cricket.In Twenty20 international cricket, he currently holds the
        world records for most career runs and most career centuries.
    </string>
    <string name="dhoni_early_life">
        Dhoni was born in Ranchi, Bihar (now in Jharkhand),and he identifies as a Hindu Rajput.His
        paternal village Lwali is in the Lamgara block of the Almora District of Uttarakhand. Dhoni\'s
        parents moved from Uttarakhand to Ranchi, where his father Pan Singh worked in junior
        management positions in MECON. Dhoni has a sister Jayanti Gupta and a brother Narendra
        Singh Dhoni.[18][19] Dhoni is a fan of Adam Gilchrist, and his childhood idols were cricket
        teammate Sachin Tendulkar, Bollywood actor Amitabh Bachchan and singer Lata Mangeshkar
    </string>
    <string name="dhoni_personal_life">
       Dhoni married Sakshi Singh Rawat, his schoolmate in DAV Jawahar Vidya Mandir, Shyamali
        [unreliable source?]a native of Dehradun, Uttarakhand, on 4 July 2010.At the time of their
        marriage, she was studying hotel management and was working as a trainee at the Taj Bengal,
        Kolkata. After the retirement of Sakshi\'s father from his tea growing business, their family
        shifted to their native place, Dehradun.
    </string>

    <string name="dhoni_early_career">
        In 1998, Dhoni was selected by Deval Sahay to play for the Central Coal Fields Limited (CCL)
        team.Till 1998 Dhoni, who was in class 12th in school, had played only school cricket and
        club cricket and no professional cricket. One of the famous episodes, when Dhoni used to play
        for CCL, was when Deval Sahay used to gift him Rs 50 for each six that he hit in Sheesh Mahal
        tournament cricket matches.Playing for CCL, he got a chance to bat up the order. He
        grabbed the opportunity and scored centuries and helped CCL move to the A division . Deval
        Sahay impressed by his hard-hitting shots and dedication, used his contacts in Bihar Cricket
        Association to push for his selection in the Bihar team.
    </string>

    <string name="dhoni_odi_career">
        The Indian ODI team in the early 2000s saw Rahul Dravid as the wicket-keeper to ensure that
        the wicket-keeper spot didn\'t lack in batting talent.The team also saw the entry of
        wicket-keeper/batsmen from the junior ranks, with talents like Parthiv Patel and Dinesh
        Karthik (both India U-19 captains) named in the Test squads.With Dhoni making a mark in
        the India A squad, he was picked in the ODI squad for the Bangladesh tour in 2004/05.
        Dhoni did not have a great start to his ODI career, getting run out for a duck on debut.
        In spite of an average series against Bangladesh, Dhoni was picked for the Pakistan ODI series

    </string>
    <string name="world_cup_2007">
        Preparations for the 2007 Cricket World Cup improved as India recorded identical 3–1
        victories over West Indies and Sri Lanka and Dhoni had averages in excess of 100 in both
        these series.India unexpectedly crashed out of the World Cup after losses to Bangladesh
        and Sri Lanka in the group stage. Dhoni was out for a duck in both these matches and scored
        just 29 runs in the tournament. After the loss to Bangladesh in 2007 Cricket World Cup, the
        house that Dhoni was constructing in his home-town Ranchi was vandalised and damaged by political
        activists of JMM.The local police arranged for security for his family as India exited the World
        Cup in the first round.
    </string>
    <string name="dhoni_t20_career">
        Dhoni was a part of India\'s first ever Twenty20 international match. He made debut against
        South Africa in December 2006. He was out for a duck but India won the match. He kept the
        wickets and effected one catch and a runout.On 12 February 2012, Dhoni made an unbeaten 44
        to guide India to their first win over Australia at Adelaide.
    </string>

</resources>
